Speaker 1: Well, I've got a friend with a fuzzy man Short little legs, but a big, big brain When I feel small or the day feels long He taps the ground like Come on, let's go on He don't need words, just a little pat He wiggles
Speaker 2: his ears while the saddle gets strapped
Me
Speaker 2: and my little horse
Speaker 3: Clip-clop, clip-clop, hooray We're friends forever in a bright bay way Through puddles, hills, and fields
Speaker 4: of fun Side by side till the day is done Bless you, son
And the
Speaker 4: tiny horse you rode in on
We pack
Speaker 5: a snack and a map is the stars Kosher carrots and a pack of cards If I trip up B-1
Speaker 3: waits for me if he gets stuck i pull him free when one feels wobbly the other still that's how you know you're a friend for real me
and my
Speaker 3: little horse clip clop clip clop hooray laughing all the worries away when the clouds go gray
Speaker 6: or the plans go wrong we turn the trouble into a song bless
you son and the
Speaker 6: tiny horse
You
Speaker 6: rollin' on
I
Speaker 7: say, hey He says, nay I say, stop He says, okay If I'm
Speaker 8: scared, he's brave If he's tired, then I'm awake
Speaker 1: Far down the road, sun
Speaker 9 (higher-pitched voice): settlin' down
Speaker 9 (higher-pitched voice): miles away from the nearest town, two best friends with nothing to do, converting my tiny horse,
now he's a
Speaker 9 (higher-pitched voice): Jew, me and
my little
Speaker 10: horse, clip-clop, clip-clop, hooray, friendship grows in every
Speaker 11: way, you don't need wings or a magic force, just a kind.
Speaker 11: and a tiny horse
Speaker 12: Me and my miniature horse Me
and my
Speaker 13: miniature horse
Me and my
Speaker 14: Clip
Speaker 15: Clop, best friends for life
Thank you.